

### **ABOUT ME**

I am a passionate frontend developer with experience in ReactJS and Angular, which allows me to turn creative designs into interactive and functional experiences. I enjoy working in teams, having successfully achieved shared goals while cultivating strong interpersonal relationships.

My enthusiasm for professional growth and the pursuit of new challenges drive me to keep expanding my skills in the frontend development universe.

#### **SKILLS**

- Html CSS SCSS Bootstrap
- GIT
- JavaScript / TypeScript
- · ReactJs NextJs
- NodeJs MongoDB
- AngularJs
- MySQL
- Scrum Methodology Kanban

#### **LANGUAGE**

English B2 in preparation for the IELTS exam.

#### **CONTACT**



Yerba Buena, Tucumán, Argentina



3815994157



joni.arriazu2@gmail.com



/JonathanArriazu



/jonathanarriazu

#### **REFERENCES**

Paulina Matheus (Human resources leader at Siltium)

- o 3875385826
- o pmatheus@siltium.com

Martín Valdez (Co-founder at Siltium)

o 3874814764

# JONATHAN ARRIAZU

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER

### **EDUCATION**

## **Udemy**

- "NextJs & React The Complete Guide" by Maximilian Schwarzmüller (May 2023)
- "Angular Avanzado: Lleva tus bases al siguiente nivel" by Fernando Herrera (February 2023)
- "Angular: De cero a experto" by Fernando Herrera (December 2022)
- "JavaScript Moderno Guía Definitiva" by Juan Pablo de la Torre Valdez (January 2022)
- "Git complete: The definitive, step-by-step guide to Git" by Jason Taylor (December 2021)
- "Aprende a crear páginas web con HTML y CSS" byDaniel lopez (June 2021)

## Full Stack Developer - Rolling Code School

September 2021 - July 2022

- Html
- CSS
- GIT
- Bootstrap
- Scrum

- JavaScript
- ReactIs
- NodeJs Express
- MongoDB

## **Agronomy Engineering - UNT**

May 2013 - December 2020

Advanced student of Agronomic Engineering

## **PROJECT EXPERIENCE**

## Software Developer - SILTIUM

October 2022 - September 2023

- Development of a multi-tenant administrative system.
  - Role: Frontend Developer using NextJs, for layout and connection to endpoints.
- Development of an administration system for a wholesale distributor.
  - Role: FullStack developer using AngularJs for frontend and .Net for backend development.

#### ReactJs, NodeJs, ExpressJs y MongoDB Project - Rolling Code

June 2022 - July 2022

Third team project for the development of a website for the publication and adoption of lost pets. We worked with ReactJs and Bootstrap for the frontend and for the backend we used NodeJs with ExpressJs. MongoDB was used as a non-relational database.

#### Vanilla JavaScript Project - Rolling Code

March 2022 - April 2022

Second team project, for the development of a website for selling video games. We worked with Vanilla JavaScript and implemented scrum methodology and use of git.

### Html, Cs & Bootstrap Project - Rolling Code

September 2021 - November 2021

First team project for the realization of the layout of a web site for PC components sales.